<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TurtleRabbit</title>
    <link>https://wsu-turtlerabbit.github.io/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content on TurtleRabbit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 17:34:23 +1100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://wsu-turtlerabbit.github.io/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Soccer training</title>
      <link>https://wsu-turtlerabbit.github.io/docs/blog/soccer-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 17:34:23 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wsu-turtlerabbit.github.io/docs/blog/soccer-training/</guid>
      <description>The software that runs locally on each robot translates requests for a robot velocity into individual motor velocities. From a centralised team controller, a computer outside the field, our robots receive the requested robot velocities, calculates the appropriate motor velocities using the geometry of the robot, and passes these resulting values to the individual controllers via a CAN bus interface. Low level control is handled by each motor controller and their firmware.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Version 1</title>
      <link>https://wsu-turtlerabbit.github.io/docs/blog/version-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 12:01:27 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wsu-turtlerabbit.github.io/docs/blog/version-one/</guid>
      <description>Robots in RoboCup SSL do not have to follow a fixed design, but they do need to comply with some general rules. Most importantly, their size is limited to a diameter of 180 mm, and a height of 150 mm. The colourful pattern on top is used by the external vision system to identify individual robots from both teams. The ball used in this competition is an orange golf ball.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Built from scratch</title>
      <link>https://wsu-turtlerabbit.github.io/docs/blog/built-from-scratch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 11:15:47 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wsu-turtlerabbit.github.io/docs/blog/built-from-scratch/</guid>
      <description>Our motor mounts hold the BLDC motor on one side, and the controller on the opposite side. In our design, they also act as the connection between base plate and mid level plate in our design. Initially, we 3D printed the motor mounts, and cut the base plates from 3 mm plywood, but for thermal and mechanical reasons we decided to machine the motor mounts from 8 mm 6061-T651 aluminium. The base plate is machined from 3 mm 6061-T6 aluminium, and the mid-level plate from 2 mm 6061-T6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling the Secrets of Black Holes: A Journey into the Heart of Darkness</title>
      <link>https://wsu-turtlerabbit.github.io/docs/posts/2023/unveiling-the-secrets-of-black-holes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 22:11:36 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wsu-turtlerabbit.github.io/docs/posts/2023/unveiling-the-secrets-of-black-holes/</guid>
      <description>In the vast expanse of the cosmos, there are few objects as mysterious and awe-inspiring as black holes. These enigmatic cosmic phenomena, once thought of as nothing more than theoretical curiosities, have now become a central focus of astronomical research. In this article, we embark on a journey deep into the heart of darkness, unraveling some of the secrets that lie within.&#xA;Black Holes: What and Why? Before delving deeper, let&amp;rsquo;s understand what a black hole actually is.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reinventing the wheel</title>
      <link>https://wsu-turtlerabbit.github.io/docs/blog/reinventing-the-wheel/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 18:16:38 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wsu-turtlerabbit.github.io/docs/blog/reinventing-the-wheel/</guid>
      <description>We use a small, “outrunner” type drone motor with a diameter of 44.5 mm, and a height of 22 mm inside each wheel. The main wheel chassis is printed in PETG, while the front and rear wheel covers are milled from 3 mm 6061-T6 aluminium. The aluminium front wheel cover is directly attached to the flat front of the BLDC motor.&#xA;Subwheels Each main wheel holds 2 rows of 15 subwheels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galactic Marvels: The Most Spectacular Nebulas in the Cosmos</title>
      <link>https://wsu-turtlerabbit.github.io/docs/posts/2023/galactic-marvels/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 11:15:17 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wsu-turtlerabbit.github.io/docs/posts/2023/galactic-marvels/</guid>
      <description>In the vast expanse of the cosmos, one cannot help but be captivated by the breathtaking beauty of nebulae. These celestial marvels are often hidden in the depths of space, waiting to be discovered and admired by astronomers and space enthusiasts alike. In this article, we will embark on a cosmic journey to explore some of the most spectacular nebulas in the cosmos, shedding light on their unique features and the mysteries they hold.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stellar Spectacles: The Wonders of Supernova Explosions</title>
      <link>https://wsu-turtlerabbit.github.io/docs/posts/2023/stellar-spectacles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 22:45:37 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wsu-turtlerabbit.github.io/docs/posts/2023/stellar-spectacles/</guid>
      <description>In the vast expanse of the cosmos, few events match the spectacle and scientific importance of supernova explosions. These awe-inspiring cosmic fireworks mark the dramatic end of a star&amp;rsquo;s life and offer profound insights into the universe&amp;rsquo;s workings. In this article, we embark on a journey to explore the wonders of supernova explosions, shedding light on their significance and the mysteries they unveil.&#xA;Supernova Explosions: Cosmic Fireworks Keyword: Supernova Explosions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Exploration&#39;s Next Frontier: The Race to Reach Mars</title>
      <link>https://wsu-turtlerabbit.github.io/docs/posts/2023/space-explorations-next-frontier/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 13:45:49 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wsu-turtlerabbit.github.io/docs/posts/2023/space-explorations-next-frontier/</guid>
      <description>The dream of reaching Mars has captured the imagination of scientists, engineers, and space enthusiasts for decades. In recent years, this dream has transformed into a tangible goal, with various space agencies and private companies embarking on missions to make it a reality. In this article, we delve into space exploration&amp;rsquo;s next frontier—the race to reach Mars.&#xA;The Martian Challenge Mars, often referred to as the &amp;ldquo;Red Planet,&amp;rdquo; has long been a subject of fascination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Beyond: Exploring the Expanding Universe</title>
      <link>https://wsu-turtlerabbit.github.io/docs/posts/2023/the-great-beyond/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 14:15:05 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wsu-turtlerabbit.github.io/docs/posts/2023/the-great-beyond/</guid>
      <description>The universe, with its vastness and complexity, has intrigued humanity for centuries. In recent decades, our understanding of the cosmos has deepened, thanks to groundbreaking discoveries about the expansion of the universe. In this article, we embark on a journey to explore the great beyond, delving into the universe&amp;rsquo;s expansion and the mysteries it unveils.&#xA;The Expanding Universe: A Cosmic Revelation Keyword: Expanding Universe&#xA;Long-term Keyword: Insights into Universe&amp;rsquo;s Expansion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cosmic Time Travel: Peering into the Universe&#39;s Past with Telescopes</title>
      <link>https://wsu-turtlerabbit.github.io/docs/posts/2022/cosmic-time-travel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 09:30:32 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wsu-turtlerabbit.github.io/docs/posts/2022/cosmic-time-travel/</guid>
      <description>In the realm of astronomy, telescopes are our time machines, allowing us to peer into the distant past of the universe. These remarkable instruments have the power to capture light that has traveled across the cosmos for millions or even billions of years. In this article, we embark on a journey of cosmic time travel, exploring how telescopes enable us to witness the universe&amp;rsquo;s history.&#xA;The Time-Traveling Telescopes Keyword: Time-Traveling Telescopes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hubble Space Telescope: 30 Years of Stunning Discoveries</title>
      <link>https://wsu-turtlerabbit.github.io/docs/posts/2022/the-hubble-space-telescope/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 09:30:32 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wsu-turtlerabbit.github.io/docs/posts/2022/the-hubble-space-telescope/</guid>
      <description>For three remarkable decades, the Hubble Space Telescope has been our eye on the universe, delivering breathtaking images and transformative scientific insights. Since its launch in 1990, the Hubble has reshaped our understanding of the cosmos and provided us with unparalleled views of distant galaxies, nebulae, and other celestial wonders. In this article, we celebrate the Hubble Space Telescope&amp;rsquo;s 30 years of stunning discoveries.&#xA;The Visionary Hubble Telescope Keyword: Hubble Space Telescope</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exoplanets: Hunting for Earth&#39;s Cosmic Cousins</title>
      <link>https://wsu-turtlerabbit.github.io/docs/posts/2022/exoplanets-hunting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 13:03:07 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wsu-turtlerabbit.github.io/docs/posts/2022/exoplanets-hunting/</guid>
      <description>In the vast tapestry of the cosmos, one of the most intriguing quests of modern astronomy is the search for exoplanets, distant celestial bodies that might bear a resemblance to our own Earth. This endeavor is driven by the tantalizing question: Could there be other habitable worlds out there? In this article, we embark on a journey to explore the captivating hunt for Earth&amp;rsquo;s cosmic cousins.&#xA;The Exoplanet Revolution Keyword: Exoplanet Revolution</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
